本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为若因私自散布传播造成法律问题 本字幕组概不负责更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组
大家字幕组
好消息...我早晨的孕吐终于不再犯了!
Good news... my morning sickness is finally over!
还有个更好的消息...我做了个
Even better news... I had a great dream
大家字幕组
关于我和碧昂斯的好梦呢
about me and Beyonc?
普鲁登斯 你们俩这婚还结着哪
Prudence, I see you two are still married.
是呀...他们都觉得我们长久不了呢
Yeah... and they said it wouldn't last.
"他们"就是指你啦
And by "they," I mean you.
这么开心的时刻来点栗子酱烤面包啊?
Care for some toast with gooseberry jam?
向我靠拢
Keep it together.
不然你吃了 我就得吃
Because when you gag, I gag.
懂的 团结一心抵制它
I got it, rock-solid.
真是美味无穷啊
It's quite tasty,
虽然看起来像痰吐在了烤面包上
although it does look like phlegm on toast.
又来了
Here we go.
我不能
I can't.
- 哦 快停下来 - 不 你先停
- Oh, you gotta stop. - No, you stop.
- 为什么你偏偏要说到痰? - 你得停下来
- Why did you say phlegm? - You gotta stop.
- 快走开! - 快拿走!
- Get it outta here! - Put it away!
让这些奇怪的英式早餐
Yeah, we might need to take a break
高抬贵手放过我们吧
on the weird British breakfast food,
至少在孩子出生之前...
at least until the baby is born...
长大之前...以及搬走以后
and grows up... and moves out.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我去别的屋吃
I'll eat it in the other room.
我猜我也应该把这些血肠带走
I'm guessing I should also take this blood sausage.
- 别恶心啦! - 呃呃呃!
- Stop it! - Uhhgh!
滚开!
No!
幸福大家庭
第一季
第四集
翻译
霉霉 xz 惊鸣
坑坑 runRrun 卷卷
校对
马来福 LilBear
轴 特效
西子耶 字母 Lynn
压制
YY 天天 大王
你买的这些姜味儿棒棒糖
These ginger lollipops you got me
对我的晨吐有很大的帮助呀
are really helping with the morning sickness.
给你秀一秀...
And look what I can do...
你的嘴是长在哪儿的?
Where do you think your mouth is?
我等不及要去农贸市场了
I can't wait to go to the farmers' market
我要去秀秀我炫酷拉风的新推车!
and show off my sweet, new ride!
哦 这位妈妈要去大采购啦
Ooh, Mama means business.
哦 我喜欢新买的手推车的味道
Ohh, I love that new cart smell.
我们应该出去走走...现在是紫色花椰菜上市的季节
We should get moving... it's purple cauliflower season,
所以市场里肯定是热闹翻天!
and it's gonna be a madhouse down there!
瞧瞧!
Look!
利兹 不好了不好了!
Lizzy, it's happening!
哦 用马桶塞一下搞定 因为我们的是节水马桶
Oh, just use the plunger. It's a low-flow toilet.
至多就5下
Five squares max.
不!那些鲸鱼 它们在海湾里交配
No! The whales, they're mating in the bay.
呃 请不要用这样的措辞
Ew, don't call it that.
那可是是真正的座头鲸在圣莫尼卡湾交配啊
No, actual humpback whales are mating in Santa Monica Bay.
那啥 如果我们动作快点 划小皮艇能近距离观赏高清无码版
Look, if we hurry, we can kayak out there and watch.
不过也别太近 不然可能会被现场氛围带进去跟着一块来一发了
Well, not too close, or you become part of the action.
不管怎样 我们已经有计划了
Anyway, we already have plans.
今天是本月第三个星期天
It's the third Sunday of the month,
知道我在说啥咩呀
if you know what I mean.
我是不能去天主教堂的
I'm not allowed in a Catholic church,
如果这是你们的计划
if that's your plan.
不 是"嗨翻天的星期天"
No, it's Sunday Funday.
我们要去最爱的农贸市场
We go to our favorite farmers' market,
在好莱坞的那个
the one in Hollywood.
- 去你的 影视城! - 哦!
- Suck it, Studio City! - Oh!
上次我去农贸市场的时候还是在泰国
Last time I was at a farmers' market was in Thailand,
然后我还以走私瓜果被控告
and I was accused of smuggling melons.
哦 在这个农贸市场同样有好戏上演
Oh, there's drama at this farmers' market, too.
厄夫 卖小松糕的家伙 是个犹太人
Irv, the muffin guy, is Jewish,
但他老婆不是
but his wife is not.
只是最近我很想去做一些刺激的冒险
It's just I've been craving a bit of adventure lately.
好吧 好吧 嗯 这个 额
Okay, okay, well, the, uh,
目前只有利兹的房间没有被我们播撒过爱的种子了
only room we haven't done it in is Lizzy's.
你们当然有
Yes, you have.
而且我当时没睡着哦
And I wasn't sleeping.
不 我的意思是
No, what I mean is
我最近过的都有点了无生趣
I've just been feeling a bit restless.
我是想说 这是我待过最久的地方
I mean, this is the longest I've stayed in one place
自从我结束了在摩洛哥做志愿者
since I was a volunteer in Morocco,
改造扒手猴的生活以后
reforming pickpocket monkeys.
哇 你的人生真是充满了冒险啊
Wow, you've lived an adventurous life.
我没办法和猴子比 除非是玩"运动冷知识" (手机游戏)
I can't compete with monkeys,unless it's sports trivia.
他们玩那个可烂了
They suck at sports trivia.
嘿 在这个偷瓜贼出现之前
Hey, you and I have had some pretty legendary adventures
我们也有过几次相当传奇的冒险啊
before old melon smuggler here showed up.
我们上次的公路之旅怎么样?
What about our last road trip?
你们是租了一辆野营车一路向前疾驰
Did you rent a camper van and just hit the open road,
让风来指引你们的方向吗？
going where the wind takes you?
差不多吧...我们租了个面包车
Close... we rented a minivan
开到了圣地亚哥
and we drove down to San Diego
清扫我阿姨的公寓
to clean out my aunt's apartment.
然后呢?
And?
然后她有好多只猫
And she had a lot of cats,
- 然后他们还挺有个性 - 啊
- and they had  attitude.- Ohh.
听着 重点是
Look, the point is,
如果你想冒险
if you're looking for adventure,
今天就是你的幸运日
today is your lucky day.
为什么这么说呢? 因为今天是星期天
How do I know? 'Cause it's Sunday,
是唯一和 "嗨翻天"在读音上押韵的一天
and that's the only day that rhymes with "Funday"!
星期一也挺押韵的
Except for Monday.
玩文字游戏的权利归我
Just leave the naming of the days to me.
嗨翻天的星期天 走起吧小婊砸们!
Sunday Funday, bitches!
没说你们
Not you guys.
太棒了!
All right!
别担心 他们还没演奏完
Don't worry, they're not finished.
就是休息个五分钟
They're just taking a five-minute chai break.
我们总是会停在这儿问候一下"谷粒和玫瑰"小乐团
We always stop and give Grains N' Roses some love.
我以前还从没见过有人能随着轻音乐扭摆呢
I've never seen anybody grind to easy listening before.
哇哦...这儿可真有点壮观
Wow... kind of a scene down here.
紫花椰菜把所有男孩儿都吸引到院子里来了
Purple cauliflower brings all the boys to the yard.
对啊...还有整车的大人
Yeah... and that bus of seniors.
哦 等一下
Oh, just wait.
我们甚至还没走到生菜那里呢
We haven't even gotten into the lettuces yet.
这仅仅是一叶障目...是的 我要说的是...
This is just the tip... yep, I'm gonna say it...
后面还有泰山 哈哈
of the "iceberg," heh.
在你俩对花生酱笑没完的时候...
While you two are giggling over nut butters...
我拿了一份当地的报纸
I picked up a local paper.
哦 那种报纸只会有广告
Oh, that paper just has ads
刊登着医用大麻和色情按摩的信息
for medical marijuana and dirty massages.
这是我最喜欢的报纸
It's my favorite paper.
来看看封面故事
And look at the cover story.
"给找刺激人士的洛杉矶指南"
"The Thrill-seekers Guide to L.A."
这就是我一直在找的!
This is exactly what I've been looking for!
看看啊 不觉得听起来特带劲儿么?
Look, doesn't this sound fun?
"在死亡峡谷高空跳伞"
"Skydiving in Death Valley."
- 哈 - 那么说是有原因的
- Huh. - Called that for a reason.
"夜登好莱坞标志"
"Climb in the Hollywood Sign at Night."
- 这个嘛... - 要是你想被谋杀的话
- Well... - If you wanna get murdered.
哦! "在马里布(加州著名海滩)滑翔"
Ooh! "Wingsuiting in Malibu."
- 我是想说... - 那就是直接进骨灰盒
- I mean... - That's a closed casket.
哦 看! 这儿有一个酒吧
Oh, look! There's a pub close by
你能在哪里喝酒和玩儿蛇
where you can have a drink and play with snakes.
如果我们快点 我们能赶上两点的喂蛇互动环节
Look, if we hurry, we can catch the 2:00 feeding.
那个其实听起来还挺有意思的
That actually sounds kinda fun.
哦 拜托 你甚至都不喜欢蛇
Oh, please, you don't even like snakes.
这个嘛 也许是因为我从来没有边喝酒边和它们玩儿过
Well, maybe 'cause I never play with them while drinking.
够了 卢克 我想说这可是"嗨翻天的星期天"啊
Enough, Luke, I mean this is Sunday Funday.
排队尝橄榄油的人越来越多了
The line for the olive oil tasting is getting longer.
他快要没有夏巴塔面包了!
He's gonna run out of ciabatta!
你有没有过轻按蛇的后背
Have you ever flipped a snake on its back
还轻挠他的肚子?
and tickled its belly?
它们真的会笑
They actually laugh.
伙计 快点
Dude, come on.
宝贝 我们走
Babe, let's go.
- 卢克! - 亲爱的!
- Luke! - Honey!
所以 这就是我的生活现状啦
So, this is my life now.
我夹在两个女人之间
I'm stuck between two women,
而且这不是像那些业余电影人拍的
and it's not the romp some amateur filmmakers
那种电影里想让你相信的那样
would have you believe.
我要跟你说的话和
I'm gonna tell you the same thing
我上周告诉我表弟的话一样
I told my cousin Chuck last week.
你的问题在于你有俩老婆
Your problem is you got two wives.
马库斯 利兹不是我老婆
Marcus, Lizzy is not my wife.
那就发短信告诉她你不回家吃晚饭了
Text her you're not coming home for dinner.
我不能那么做...不回家吃饭得5点之前就告诉她
Can't do that... would've needed to call her before 5:00.
你看 一个月前
Look, a month ago,
你只需要考虑怎么
you only had to worry about
让利兹开心就行了
keeping Lizzy happy.
现在呢 你有了普鲁登斯
And now, you have Prudence,
一个我猜测能以拉拉做不到的方式
who I'm guessing makes you happy
让你爽歪歪的人
in a way a lesbian friend can't.
从技术上来讲 拉拉做得到...
Technically, lesbians can...
她们只是不想这样做
they just don't want to.
我的意思是普鲁登斯想尝试新事物
I'm just saying Prudence wants to try new things,
所以你或许需要跟上她的步伐
so you might wanna get on board with her
在她觉得你无聊之前
before she gets bored with you.
你觉得她会觉得我无聊
You think she's gonna get bored with me?
我都觉得你无聊
I'm  bored with you.
我们什么事情也不干!
We never do anything!
只有工作 工作 工作
It's just work, work, work.
因为我们就是在这里工作啊
Because this is where we work.
我的意思是...
My point is...
时不时的 给人家点惊喜
one of these days, surprise me.
晚饭请假的事真是任重道远啊
Dinner goes a long way.
总而言之
To sum it up,
如果普鲁登斯不那么痴迷于寻找刺激
if Prudence wasn't so obsessed with her thrill-seeking,
我和鲁克就会度过一个经典的"嗨翻天的星期天"
Luke and I would've had a classic Sunday Funday,
我就不用一直吃商店卖的廉价小胡萝卜
and I wouldn't be stuck eating store-bought baby carrots
像个普通的小婊砸一样
like a common whore.
嘿 一条育儿小贴士
Hey, a little parenting tip:
你如果要哄小孩睡觉
if you ever need to put that baby to sleep,
就给他讲这个农贸市场的故事吧
tell this farmers' market story.
好了 我把小公主城堡从车上拿下来了
Okay, I dropped off the princess castle
放在后院 下次你照看乔吉
in the backyard for the next time
就可以用了
you babysit Georgie.
那儿风有点大
And it's kinda windy out there,
我还没有合适的工具 所以...
and I didn't have the proper tools, so...
城堡整个塌了也不用太惊讶
wouldn't be surprised if the whole thing fell apart.
等一下 老姐 你们为啥把城堡玩具放在这？
Wait, Sissy, why are you guys leaving a play castle here?
你们自己家都没有
You don't even have one for her at your place.
我们希望她在你家玩的开心
We want your house to be fun for her.
特别是今年夏天我们去火人节的时候
Especially this summer when we go to Burning Man.
哦 顺便告诉你 这个夏天
Oh, by the way, you're watching her
我们去火人节的时候你得照顾她
this summer when we go to Burning Man.
当然
Of course.
我希望我没错过农贸市场故事
I hope I didn't miss the rest of that
的剩下部分
great farmers' market story.
- 她还没说完 - 见鬼
- She's still going. - Damn.
还有一件事
And the other thing is,
是他把农贸市场介绍给我
he introduced me to this farmers' market.
我可是一直住在影视城这片市区的哎!
I was all Studio City, all the time!
放松 老妹儿 你不会失去鲁克的
Relax, Sissy. You're not losing Luke.
我确信这只是他一时没想清楚
I'm sure his judgment's all clouded.
英国人在床上做一些很前卫的事
British people do some funky things in bed.
我只是听说过
I've heard.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
鲁克不会变成另一个人
Luke's not gonna turn into a different person.
我知道 你是对的
I know, you're right.
天了噜 你是谁?
Oh, my God. Who are you?
看起来像基版超级英雄
Kinda looks like a gay superhero.
真理 正义 还有美国式的"嘿!"
Truth, justice, and the American "Heeey!"
告诉我你不是从飞机上跳下来的
Please tell me you're not jumping out of an airplane.
飞机多危险
Planes are dangerous.
我要从悬崖上跳下来
I'm jumping off a cliff.
我要做普鲁登斯那个清单上
I'm doing that wingsuiting thing
的滑翔挑战
from Prudence's list.
有降落伞吗?
Is there a parachute?
- 我估摸着有吧 - 你怎么着陆?
- I think so. - How do you land?
不清楚
Not sure.
好吧 那准没好下场
Well, that's not gonna end well.
我目睹过你看个奥运会
I've seen you sprain your ankle
都能崴脚的经历
watching the Olympics.
放轻松 我还得等好几个礼拜
Relax, I don't actually soar off a cliff
才会从悬崖上跳下去呢
for a couple weeks.
这个真是太危险了 他们都让你先
It's so dangerous they make you practice
在一个墙壁有软垫的风洞里练习
in a wind tunnel with padded walls.
你有没有照过镜子啊?
Have you looked at yourself?
你这德性可以跳过前面直接到有软垫的墙壁就行了
'Cause you could skip right to the padded walls.
咱们走吧...乔治在车里等着呢
Let's go... Georgie's waiting in the car
而且还开着空调
with the air conditioning on.
放轻松 美帝人民
Relax, America.
哥们 你绝对会死翘翘的哟
Dude, you're gonna die.
哦 我的天呐 我都不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe
你竟然会考虑要做这个
you're even considering doing this,
尤其是 你就要做爸爸了
especially since you're about to be a father.
是啊 不过我也是普鲁登斯的丈夫呀
Yeah, but I'm also a husband to Prudence.
我结婚誓词上说过的 "直到死亡将我们分开"
I made a vow: "Till death do us part."
那也不是今天就要死啊!
That doesn't mean today!
好吧 如果普鲁登斯从桥上跳下去 你也跳?
Okay, if Prudence jumped off a bridge, would you?
其实我们下周正要做这个
We're actually doing that next week.
- 你到底有啥毛病啊?! - 我没毛病啊!
- What's wrong with you?! - Nothing!
我...就是想稍稍改变一下现状
I... just wanna change things up a little.
我这一辈子都在保龄球馆上班
I've worked at a bowling alley my whole life.
做过最有异国范儿的事就是
The most exotic thing I've ever done
在夫勒斯诺的时候和一个1/2亚洲血统的妹子啪啪啪
was sleep with a half-Asian girl in Fresno.
你和张明 罗宾逊啪啪啪了?
You slept with Chang Ming Robinson?
这不是重点 不过 是的 两次呢
Not important, but, yes, twice.
听着 鲁克 开阔视野
Listen, Luke, there are other ways
还有其他办法的 不是吗?
to expand your horizons, okay?
你的图书馆借书卡就在抽屉里呀
Your library card is just sitting in your drawer.
告诉你个消息哦...
I got news for you...
去图书馆 不在清单上
going to the library, not on the list.
市中心那个都不在吗?
Not even the one downtown?
要进那个图书馆得经过金属探测器安检呢
You have to go through a metal detector.
听着 你已经娶了普鲁登斯了
Look, you already got Prudence to marry you.
你还在试图证明什么呢?
What are you trying to prove?
我在试图留住她
I'm trying to keep her.
- 啥? - 呃...
- What? - Uhh...
我只是不想让她觉得我无聊
I just don't want her to get bored with me.
觉得你无聊?
Bored with you?
是啊 你也看到她过得是什么样的日子了
Yeah. You've seen the life she's lived.
她啥都做过了 哪都去过了
She's done everything, and she's been everywhere.
你知道她什么时候会真的觉得你无聊么?
You know when she's really gonna get bored?
当你挂了的时候!
When you're dead!
哦 别那么大惊小怪的
Oh, don't be so dramatic!
你真的要去做?
Are you seriously gonna do this?
是的! 今天我参加培训
Yeah! Today I train,
明天 我漫步云端
tomorrow, I taste the clouds.
是时候展翅高飞了 亲爱的!
It's time to fly, baby!
鲁克! 利兹!
Luke! Lizzy!
哦 我的天呐!
Oh, my God!
我的亲娘四舅老爷啊
Oh, my God.
不知怎么的这话对你这身打扮都是夸赞了
And somehow that's flattering on you.
他会好起来吗?
Is he gonna be all right?
这个嘛 他有些轻微脑震荡
Well, he has a slight concussion,
肩膀脱臼
he dislocated his shoulder,
我们不得不打麻药才给他把肩膀弄回去
and we had to put him under to reset it.
其实...也不是不得不
Well... we didn't have to,
但是这么大个汉子哭起来真是不忍直视
but it's hard to watch a grown man cry.
我还需要知道他的一些信息
I'm gonna need some more information from him.
哦! 好的
Oh! Yes...
这是他的保险卡
Here is his insurance card,
还有他之前医生的电话
and a number to his primary doctor,
还有他还是个小可爱时候的萌照
and an adorable picture of him as a baby.
你好呀 小可爱
Oh, hello...
你是他妻子咯?
So, you're the wife?
不 我才是哈
Oh, no, I'm his wife.
我是他的"拉"蜜啦
Yeah, I'm his lesbian best friend.
而且还怀着他的宝宝
She's having his baby.
我们住一起的
We all live together.
我现在算明白他为什么想自杀了
Now I can see why he tried to kill himself.
生日是什么时候呢
Okay, uh, date of birth.
呃 我觉得他应该是冬天出生的
Um... I believe he was a winter baby.
是六月十九号好吗
It's June 19th.
在澳大利亚这就是冬天
That's winter in Australia.
他对什么东西过敏吗?
Does he have any allergies?
他喝了龙舌兰就会变得毛手毛脚的
He gets a little "handsy" on tequila.
他不能用青霉素 不能吃蘑菇
He can't have penicillin, and he can't eat mushrooms,
不过只是他自己声称过敏啦
which he says is an allergy,
其实只是不喜欢而已
but he just doesn't like them.
你造吗 其实我只是假装在写
You know what, I'm just gonna move my pen around,
好让你们以为我把最后一句记下来了
make you think I wrote that last part down.
听着 普鲁登斯 这里交给我吧
Look, Prudence, I've got this
如果你想回家去
if you wanna go home and change
把你的热气球装换下来
out of your hot air balloon.
不 不用 我觉得
No, that's all right, I think Luke would
鲁克醒来的时候一定很想见到我
want to see his wife when he wakes up.
看 他在表示赞同哎
See? He agrees with me.
才不是 他在痛的时候才会发出这种声音
No, that's the noise he makes when he's in pain.
他感觉不舒服了 得把他摇起来坐
He's uncomfortable. He needs to be propped up.
我才是每晚和他睡一起的人
Well, I sleep with him every night,
他喜欢平躺着睡
and he prefers to be flat on his back.
可能只是因为你是谁在他上面呢
Maybe if you're on top of him.
他会侧卧睡来清干喉咙
But I know that he's prone to dry throat
因为春假时他做急性腺体切除手术时我是在场的
because I was there for his emergency adenoid surgery
我还费了老大劲才找到一个
during spring break, and try finding a doctor
除了隆胸就什么都不会的医生
who does anything but breast implants in Tampa.
你可能是比我认识他久一点
Well, you may have known him longer,
但是根据在内华达州的时候
but according to the state of Nevada
那个给我们证婚的前妓女
and the former prostitute who married us,
我才是她的合法妻子
I'm legally his wife.
呵呵 一个都不知道丈夫生日的妻子!
Yeah, a wife who doesn't know her husband's birthday!
但我知道他最喜欢的一集"星球大战"是
Well, I know his favorite "Star Wars"
"帝国反击战"
is "Empire Strikes Back."
得了吧 所有人都最喜欢这集
Oh, that's everybody's favorite!
利兹 把遥控器给我
Lizzy, give it to me!
不 给我
No, you give it to me!
利兹 有些时候
Lizzy, you've got to hand over the reins
你该要把选择权交给卢克
to Luke at some point!
照顾他如今是我的职责了好吗!
It's my job to look after him now.
噢真的吗 你可照顾得真好啊
Oh, really? Well, great job looking after him, Prudence,
要不是因为你
because, if it wasn't for you,
他也不会神志不清地躺在医院里
he wouldn't be lying unconscious in a hospital bed,
就为了取悦你
trying to impress you!
这不是真的
That's not true.
这就是事实
Yes, it is!
他以前从来没穿过滑翔服
He doesn't wingsuit,
也没有跳过伞或者潜过水
and he's never skydived or dove or "doven"
不像你过去那样搞空中飞人的把戏
or however you skydive in the past!
他只是想向你证明他是爱冒险的
He was just trying to prove to you that he's adventurous.
他确实是呀
But he is adventurous.
我是说 在床上 我们...
I mean, sexually, we do...
偏题了好吗!
That's not what I'm talking about!
听着 他就是在拼命迎合你的喜好
Look, he just was going along with what you wanted to do
因为他害怕你会觉得他无聊
because he was scared that you were gonna get bored with him.
搭把手啊
You coming?
成功的时候总是没人看见
Of course, when no one's here.
我现在都能独自去浴室了
So, I just completed my first solo trip
我猜我们大家
to the bathroom, so I guess we're all
都对此深感欣慰
pretty happy about that.
既然你都好差不多了 我想我可以说了
Now that you're okay, I think I can say
我们都从这次经历中收获了点啥
we both got something out of this.
你开始学飞 而我是对的
You got to fly, and I got to be right...
这对我来说 和飞一样爽
which, for me, is like flying.
卢克 我给你做了我妈出了名的秘制蔬菜汤
Luke, I made you my mum's famous vegetable soup recipe.
其实就是水和胡萝卜
It's just water and a carrot.
我们没种出别的来
We didn't have much growing up.
不过这里面可是满满的爱呦
But there's plenty of love in there.
虽然主要的原料还是水
But the main ingredient is water.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是普鲁登斯啊
I'm Prudence.
我是你老婆
I'm your wife.
我开玩笑的!
I'm kidding!
一个关于脑震荡后的小幽默啦
A little post-concussion humor.
你应该看看 利兹提到宝宝
You should've been there when Lizzy mentioned the baby,
然后我说 "我们做过了?" 以后她的表情
and I said, "We went through with that?"
是啊 不过还是他幽你一默的时候更搞笑
Yeah, but it's so much funnier when he does it to you.
好吧 我在想我的肋骨一长好...
Anyway, I was thinking, once my ribs fuse back...
我们就能继续去完成你清单上的项目了
we can start checking stuff off your list again.
或者 我们可以试一个别的清单
Or we could try another list.
看这个...
Look at this...
"全城十大最适宜静坐的地方"
"Ten Best Places to Sit Quietly Around the City."
这样看来 市中心有一片干草坪
Apparently, there's a dry patch of grass downtown
是必去的胜地啊
that's a must-try.
你干嘛读《美国退休者协会杂志》?
Why are you reading "AARP" magazine?
嘿 那是我的
Hey, that's mine.
这期的封面故事可是莉莉 汤普琳(美国演员)
There was a Lily Tomlin cover story.
我没明白 "一片干草坪?"
I'm sorry, "a dry patch of grass?"
- 这到底怎么回事儿? - 没事儿啊
- What's going on? - Nothing.
只不过是我已经有过了很多次的冒险经历
It's just that I've had plenty of adventure.
也许是时候静下心来了
Maybe it's time to calm things down.
学学做数独啦...或者看看"海军罪案调查处"
Learn Sudoku... or watch "NCIS."
可是这不是你风格啊
But that's not you.
嗯 事实证明滑翔也不是你的风格
Well, it turns out wingsuiting isn't really you.
你到底想说什么啊?
What are you talking about?
我意思是 没错 我是出了点小事故
I mean, sure, I had a little accident,
而且在呼吸 说话和嘘嘘的时候会有点疼
and it hurts when I breathe, talk, and pee...
但这不代表我不会再尝试新鲜事物啊
but it doesn't mean I wanna stop trying new things.
好吧 那你为什么要担心我会觉得你无聊啊?
Well, then why are you worried that I'm gonna get bored with you?
谁说我担心你会觉得我无聊啊?
Who said I was worried about you getting bored with me?
你告诉她了?
You told her that?
因为你告诉她了
Because you told her that.
问题是 你为什么不告诉我
And the question is, why couldn't you tell me?
不是这样 普鲁登斯 等一下 听我解释啊!
No, Prudence, wait. Let me explain!
看看你都干什么好事了?!
What did you do?!
普鲁登斯!
Prudence!
我真是难以置信你居然告诉了普鲁登斯
I can't believe you told Prudence
我担心她会觉得我无聊的事
I was scared she was gonna get bored with me.
你是不是还给她看了那张有个夏天
Did you also show her pictures of me from the summer
我又胖又满身是糖霜的照片?
I was fat and had frosted tips?
没有! 还没聊到那么久远呢
No! There's no coming back from that.
那你想我怎么做?
What did you want me to do?
你当时正跳进一个那么危险的火坑
You were jumping through very dangerous hoops,
还想成为那种你原本不是的人
trying to be someone you're not.
利兹 我没成为另一个人
Lizzy, I'm not a different person.
我就是想试着突破一下我们的生活方式
I was just trying to break the mold a little.
可是我喜欢我们的方式
But I like our mold.
它一直伴随着我们
It's shaped like us.
是啊 但现在我们要习惯普鲁登斯在我们之间插一脚
Well, now we have to fit Prudence inside us.
或者换个方式表达这个意思
Or a different way of saying that.
不过我懂了 不再仅仅只有我们两个人了
But I get it, it's not just the two of us anymore.
我感觉好糟糕啊
I feel bad.
我不应该和她说 你的事故是她的错
I shouldn't have told her your accident was her fault.
我应该和她说 我和你说过的话的
I should've just told her what I told you.
我们找到她的时候 应该把这些都告诉她
And when we find her, we should tell her that.
你们已经告诉我了
You just did.
哦!
Oh!
我明白了...你是英国人
I get it... you're British,
所以当你不开心的时候 你就去找离你最近的城堡
so when you're upset, you find the nearest castle.
不 我们不高兴的时候就会喝两杯 一醉解千愁
No, when we're upset, we drink and don't let it show.
不过借酒浇愁愁更愁
Until we really let it show.
宝贝 我不是故意让你不高兴的
Baby, I didn't mean to get you upset.
我只是想让你觉得我很了不起
I just wanted you to think I'm awesome.
而且我猜我只是习惯了和利兹
And I guess I'm just used to talking to Lizzy
无话不说
about everything.
无话不说?
Everything?
甚至是我们昨晚做那件事情时候用了...
Even that thing we did last night with the...
- 不包括那个 - 他没和我说那个
- Not that. - He did not tell me that.
我只是忍不住去想 如果我像她一样了解你
I just can't help feeling that none of this would've happened
那所有这些都不会发生
if I knew you like she does.
她遥遥领先你30年
She's had a 30-year head start.
这也是为什么有时候对我来说
Which is why it's a little tough for me
和别人共享他会有点困难
to share him sometimes.
大部分时候
Most times.
任何时候!
All the times!
你要知道 我永远都不会让你因为我受伤
You have to know I'd never want you to get hurt because of me.
好吧 除了你这么要求的时候
Well, unless you were asking for it,
比如耳光式的卧室情趣 之类的情况
like a slappy bedroom kind of situation.
我还以为你们是在那儿鼓掌
I thought you guys were clapping in there,
而且那个声音烦死我了
and  that  bothered me.
不是你想的 昨天晚上确实是在鼓掌
No, last night was actual clapping.
我大展了雄风
I did a really good job.
我是真的很爱你...所以你可以什么都和我说
I really do love you... and you can tell me anything.
我知道...我爱你
I know... and I love you.
"我爱你哦"
"I love you."
"我也爱你呢"
"I love you, too."
我想身边有个找刺激的人也挺不错
And I guess it's kinda good to have
因为我俩肯定不会做这种事
a thrill-seeker around, 'cause it's certainly not us!
你的冒险大胆程度可远超你对你自己的评价
You're bigger risk-takers than you're giving yourselves credit for.
你是在说我的羊毛衫?
Are you talking about my cardigan?
因为我不太确定穿它是不是需要很大胆
'Cause I wasn't sure about it.
不是 我在说事实
No, I'm talking about the fact
你们要一起有个孩子了
you're having a baby together.
这很勇敢
It's quite brave.
你们正在创造属于你们自己定义的家庭
You're creating your own definition of family.
谢啦
Thanks.
这么说你觉得穿这件羊毛衫是疯了
So you think the cardigan's crazy.
我的确不是特别喜欢啦
It's not my favorite.
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
哇哦...爬上好莱坞的标志
Wow... climbing up to the Hollywood Sign
可真是一个好主意 利兹
was a really good idea, Lizzy.
我真是不敢相信 我竟然完成了恐怖清单上的一项
I can't believe I did something off the scary list.
做个坏人感觉真好
Feels good to be bad.
知道还有什么会让你感觉很好么?
Know what else feels good?
带着你伤痕累累的肋骨徒步爬上这儿来
Doing that hike up here with bruised ribs.
就不能等个两三天么?
Couldn't have waited two, three days?
哦 可怜的亲亲
Oh, poor baby.
我会帮你振作起来的
I'll help you get back on your feet.
你是想说"骑在我背上吧"?
Don't you mean "back on my back"?
- 喔 - 嗯...
- Oh... - Mmm...
彼以国士待我，我以国士待之，用过免费优质字幕服务，而又有能力的人，有义务将这个免费服务做下去。若有心加入我们 联系QQ群 428872140 更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博 @大家字幕组
大家字幕组
你们这样让我支持你俩在一起真是好难
You make it so hard to root for you two.
大家字幕组
你知道么 如果你离得非常非常近
You know, if you look really, really close,
你就可以分辨出
you can just make out
农贸市场的那些帐篷啦
the tents of the farmers' market.
大家字幕组
利兹...
Lizzy...
我真是不敢相信 30年来我们居然没这么做过
I can't believe in 30 years we've never done this.
看看我们...这是我们第一次
Look at us... this is our first
一起进行真正的冒险
real adventure together.
对啊 是这样
Yeah, it is.
尤其是当这种冒险还是违法的时候
Especially since it's illegal.
是啊
Yeah.
等等 你说啥?!
Wait, what?!